辛普森一家
第二十四季 第九集
SPS辛普森一家字幕组倾情呈现
字幕仅供学习交流之用 本片版权归FOX所有
去骨顺发诊所
享受小清新的无骨生活
假期回来老师居然没变胖
翻译: 症 偏执绝非过错 大白 大曦瓜
校对&后期: 旗木 大头 盖罗  监制: MarcoII
全世界最好的爷爷
欢迎加入 SPS 辛普森一家字幕组 参与翻译后期
详情搜索 Google 或 新浪微博
机灵宝贝学习园地
想摆脱孩子 把他扔到学习园地
学习园地?
Learn Zone?
老妈 你可说要带我们去有意思的地方啊
Mom, you said we were going someplace fun.
是啊 妈妈 你说过的
Yeah, Mom, you promised!
Homer 我告诉过你别叫我"妈妈"
Homer, I told you, don't call me "Mom."
很抱歉 Simpson太太
Sorry, Mrs. Simpson.
抓稳
活体娃娃机
这不是什么学习园地吧
This isn't a learn zone.
讨厌 我看分明就是游乐园
Darn it, it's a fun place!
为最大程度确保安全
For maximum safety,
孩子们必须都戴上反诱拐手镯
all children must wear anti-kidnapping bracelets.
你真会为这种倒霉孩子付赎金?
Is this a kid you'd pay ransom for?
老爸 如果歹徒寄你一只我的耳朵 你咋办?
Dad, what would you do if you got my ear in the mail?
不好说 拿来喂狗?
I don't know. Feed it to the dog?
别忘了裹层奶酪
You'd have to wrap cheese around it.
还用得着你教我怎么把你喂狗
Don't you tell me how to feed you to the dog!
跳跳床投篮
跳跳床小憩
双重跳跳床
他们去哪里了?
Where do they go?
欢迎来到摩门教堂
Welcome to the Mormon Church,
全美最负盛名的邪教团体
America's most respectable cult.
盯着点孩子们 Homer
Keep an eye on the kids, Homer.
我能一直盯着那孩子么?
Can I keep an eye on that kid?
他可真厉害
He's fabulous.
盯着Bart和Lisa
Bart and Lisa.
每次都只能盯自己的孩子
Oh! It's always my kids.
跑哪儿去了?
Where'd they go?
还差一点
Almost.
我勒个去
Holy moley.
搞什么...?!
What the...?!
没戏了
Oh, it's hopeless!
什么没戏了?
What's hopeless?
我认识你么?
Who the hell are you?
- 老爸 快上来 快点 - 求你求你求你了
- Dad, come up, come up! - Pretty, pretty please!
绝对没门儿 这玩意儿塞不下我这个头
Absolutely not! My adult frame is simply too large.
- 上来 老爸 - 不 休想
- Come on, Dad! - No! Never!
你们赢了 我这就上去
Fine. Here I come.
我爬
Crawling.
好痛苦
So... painful.
鸭步
Duck walk.
更要命啊
Infinitely worse.
只不过是想乐一乐
Only wanted...to be fun.
你会安息的
Soon you'll know peace.
我成功了 孩子们
I made it, kids!
我是趣学堡之王
I am king of Learnington Castle!
你上当了
We tricked you.
够不够吃 呆子
Eat Nerf, Homeboy!
一点也不幼稚
Real... mature...!
Ralphie 脱鞋
Ralphie! Shoes.
快餐柜
这儿有啥好玩的?
What cool kid thing's in here?
没熊孩子 好玩就在于此
No kids. That's what's cool.
我这部手机 特别的小
I have a phone. It's very tiny.
贫穷没啥丢人的 伙计
Ain't no shame in being poor, boy.
真正丢人的 是无知
What's pitiful is if you is ignorant.
这些老鼠用的枕头可以随便带走么?
Is these mice pillows here for the taking?
速溶糖
我讨厌在这儿上班
I hate working here.
至少在Krusty汉堡店
At least at Krustyburger,
你可以烫伤自己然后回家休息
you could burn yourself and go home.
有儿童未经许可擅自离开
Unauthorized child departure.
启动封锁模式
Lockdown mode initiated.
又一个熊孩子跑了
Another stupid kid got out.
我没法跟老板汇报
I can't tell the manager.
我就是老板 好吗?
I am the manager. Duh!
激光枪战
我们被关起来啦
We're locked in!
这些激光枪除了会射红光 没半点用
These lasers are nothing more than colored lights!
冷静 大家 冷静
Calm down, everyone. Calm down.
我相信马上会有人来救我们出去
I'm sure they'll have us out of here soon.
在等待的过程中不如我们
Until then, why don't we bond
坐下起分享各自的分娩经历吧
by sharing our childbirth experiences.
护士对我可好了
The nurses were so great.
我老公一刻都没松开我的手
My husband held my hand the whole time.
怎样? 坐下来友好地交流就足以让我们安然度过危机
See? All you need to get through a crisis is a little friendly conversation.
相信爸爸们那边也是同样的情况
Bet you the dads are doing the same thing.
快餐柜的玻璃都碎了
The sneeze guard is broken!
法律不复存在
There is no law!
我只是过来接女儿回家
I just came here to pick up my daughter.
但现在我要把你们杀光光
But now I'm gonna kill you all!
别把外套落下 宝贝
Don't forget your jacket, sweetie.
鲜爆米花
快滚出来 混蛋
Get out of there, you!
做梦
Never!
热黄油
是黄油
Mmm. Butter.
玉米片奶酪
棉花糖
一圈一圈又一圈
Round and round.
自由近在咫尺
Freedom!
快点离开这里 快点
Let's get out of here! Come on!
一群蛮子 原来我们都是人面兽心的蛮子
Apes. Deep down, we're all savage apes.
放灵魂出窍吧 Homer
Leave your body, Homer.
那是什么鬼玩意?
What the hell was that?
之前那事给你留下的阴影不小
You've been through a traumatic experience.
你确定今天能回去上班吗?
Are you sure you want to go to work today?
我都放了八个月的假了
Well, I've taken eight months off.
也该是时候回归正轨了
It's time to get back on the horse.
嘿 邻居 你的门垫看起来有点脏了
Hey, neighbor, your welcome mat's looking a little dusty.
要不要我来给你擦干净点
Mind if I come over and sweeten your greetin'.
给你擦干净点
Sweeten your greetin'!
Sweeten your greetin'.
三个Ned能成虎哦
Three Neds are better than one!
我不想嚼舌头 但这是我真正的脑袋
I hate to be a nag, but this is my real head.
我想 在我们所谓文明的面具下
I guess, despite all our so-called civilization,
混乱的暗流就如网络警匪剧里
anarchy lurks around every corner,
那些多种族街头匪帮一样潜伏在每一个角落
like a racially-diverse street gang on a network cop show.
朋友 你是第一批体验到W.R.O.L.的人之一
My friend, you just experienced W.R.O.L. firsthand.
嘿嘿 没看标语吗 哥们? 别说缩略词
Hey, hey, read the sign, pal, no acronyms.
禁说          缩略语
这条对你们也一样
And that goes for the rest of youse, too!
OK OK
Okay, okay.
民主党创始人之一 据说是发明OK一词的人
嘿 在这酒吧里 你得说"老肯德胡克"
Hey, in this bar, we say "Old Kinderhook!"
W.R.O.L.是什么东西?
What's W.R.O.L.?
它就是"无法无天"的缩写
It means "Without the Rule of Law."
混乱 文明时代的终结
Anarchy. The end of civilization.
很快就会来到美国 来到你身边
Coming soon to an America near you.
美国怎么会灭亡
America can't collapse!
我们就和古罗马一样强大
We're as powerful as ancient Rome!
得了 看看这个吧
Ah, take a look at this.
现代世界前进的脚步
The modern world--
犹如钢铁洪流般不可阻挡
an inexorable march of progress.
真棒
Sweet.
真是这样吗?
Or is it?
我们是现行体系下的奴隶
We're slaves to the system.
博士 历史学教授
如果关掉超市 我们将会挨饿
Close the supermarket, and we starve.
如果没有自来水 我们就只能喝猫血
Cut off the tap, we drink our cat's blood.
石油峰值 | 本地农产品灭绝 | 本·伯南克(美联储主席)
太阳风暴 | 十七年蝉 | 致命的巨魔
谁将在这新世界活下去?
Who will survive in this new world?
唯有有备之人才有生存之权力
The man who is prepared.
剧               终
©版权所属 你们都将受死制片公司
老天啊
Oh, my God!
这段来历不明 未标日期的视频
This unsourced, undated video
居然让我茅塞顿开
has convinced me beyond any doubt!
我就是你在碰上麻烦时需要找的人
And I'm the guy you want to know when the stuff hits the fan.
嘿 伙计 没必要这么大声吧
Hey, man, no need to almost swear.
跟我来吧
Come with me.
好吧 既然Homer不在
Well, Homer's gone.
在他回来前我们先进入发呆模式吧
Let's all go into our suspended state till he gets back.
Herman枪械店
Homer 这是春田备战团的其他成员
Homer, meet the Springfield Preppers.
前皮士? (谐音 指守旧者) 见鬼 我不喜欢你们
Preppies? Oh, I hate you guys!
我们城市人在为建设社会添砖加瓦时
Always partying on deck with your Docksiders
你们却和那些游手好闲的蠢蛋一块花天酒地
while us townies are scrubbing the bilge!
不是前皮士 是备战团
Not preppies. Preppers.
但你的憎恨着实令我喜欢
But I like your hatred.
我根本不知道为啥会憎恨
It's based on nothing.
太棒了
That's super.
现在 Homer 发生E.M.P袭击时你会怎么做?
Now, Homer, what would you do in the case of an E.M.P.?
他说的是电磁冲击波
Electromagnetic pulse.
一股能让全国上下的
A burst of radiation
电路系统全部断电的电流放射
that knocks out every electrical system in the country.
我会割腕自杀
I'd slash my wrists.
但没有电子刀 你要我怎么办?
But how, without my electric knife?!
自杀又不一定要用电
There is an alternative to suicide.
我真想不到别的办法
Mm. I can't conceive of any.
我们会教你能在任何危机中幸存的技巧
We can teach you the skills you need to survive any crisis.
只希望你对你的备战行动严加保密
All we ask is that you keep your prepping secret.
我们可没地方收纳所有的无备之徒
We won't have room for all the unprepared.
别担心 我可是个守口如瓶的人
Don't worry. I'm very good at keeping secrets.
末日来了 50年纪念版
审判迫在眉睫
"Impending doom."
看什么呢 老爸?
What you reading, Dad?
亲爱的 一切都好
Honey, everything's fine.
没什么大惊小怪的
There's nothing to worry about.
通常大人这样说时
When grown-ups say that,
肯定都是有事情不对劲的
it means there is something to worry about.
去吹你的萨克斯吧
Just go play your saxophone.
马上你就吹不成了
While you can.
这话什么意思?
What does that mean?
秘密?! 我这可没什么秘密
Secrets? I have no secrets!
好好享受这段不久之后
Just enjoy this golden time
你就拼命想记住的美好时光吧
you will soon cling desperately to the memory of.
闻闻面包的味道吧
Smell some bread!
如果你读到这个 我的剑心正指向你
当我们向南进发后
When things go south,
那些盲目的暴民会把镇上所有的超市洗劫一空
the sheeple will clean out every supermarket in town.
典型的无脑
Typical sheeple.
你是不是在吃我的粮食
Uh... are you eating my grain?
好像是吧
Maybe.
这里面可是有五磅粮食的
That was a five-pound bag!
是啊 但如果回家称体重
Yeah, but I'll go home, weigh myself,
我会发现自己增重了六磅
and I'll have gained six pounds.
话说是怎么回事?
What's that about?
♪ 准备 准备 准备 ♪
♪ Prep, prep, prep. ♪
嘿 老爸 我们是要去野营吗?
Hey, Dad, are we going camping?
我觉得敞开式的车库并不是一个很好的藏身之地
I guess an open garage isn't the best hiding place.
怎么了? 又开始发疯了么?
What's up? Going crazy again?
怎么可能
I wish.
儿子 给你解释这一切最好的方法
Son, the best way to explain this is
就是给你看部少儿不宜的电影
to show you some age-inappropriate movies.
距离末日还有35分钟
冰雪世界: 洛杉矶
Kathy Griffin 末日也无法让我停止
(美国女演员 曾出演电影《劲舞不停》)
火山行星
好了 你从这些末日后电影系列中学到了什么?
So, what have you learned so far
from our post-apocalyptic movie marathon?
那些自称牧师或者执事的人没个好东西
Guys who call themselves Preacher or Deacon are very bad.
水就是钱 除此之外汽油也是钱
Water is money,unless gasoline is money.
即使有很多像剃刀般锋利的东西
And even though lots of things are razor-sharp,
也没人剃胡子了
no one ever shaves.
好莱坞可算把你教好了 乖儿子
Hollywood has taught you well, my son.
我们继续看吧
Now let's push play.
现在Beverly山的冰封主教
Now the Ice Bishop of Beverly Hills
将告诉你们寒冷的真谛
will teach you the true meaning of cold!
我是从一个温暖的地带来的人
I have come from a place where the land is warm,
在那里唯一的冰是一种叫做冰盒的东东制造的
and the only ice is made by machines called... fridge-ra-torrs.
冰盒 冰盒
Fridge-ra-torrs! Fridge-ra-torrs!
冰盒
Fridge-ra-torrs!
他们是不是在说冰箱呢?
Aren't they just saying "refrigerator"?
不要质疑Tom Skerritt的智慧 (美国演员)
Do not question the wisdom of Tom Skerritt.
就是这儿了 Homer
Here it is, Homer.
春田备战团的最高机密逃生地
The Springfield Preppers' top secret Bug-Out Retreat.
你们的世纪末伊甸园比我现在的还好
Your end of the world is better than my during the world.
Homer 我们都知道美国的毁灭将在3个月内发生
Homer, we all know America's collapse is about three months away.
最多6个礼拜
Six weeks at most.
总会有个小闹钟
There's always one alarmist.
不管怎样 当四骑士出现的时候
Anyway, when the Four Horsemen ride,
我希望你和你的伙计来这里和我们一起待着
we want you and your collaterals right here with us.
听着 我必须知道
Uh, listen, I've got to know--
你们对我这么好的原因
you're not just being nice to me
不光是要在紧要关头用我的脂肪做蜡烛吧?
because in a pinch you could make candles from my fat?
那是很大一部分原因
Well, that is a big part of it.
没关系 我知道自己几斤几两
It's okay. I know what I am.
我找不到我们买的苏打饼干 果汁盒子 黄油刀
I can't find all our cereal crackers, juice boxes,the butter brush...
很多东西可能在我们搬家的时候弄丢了
Um... a lot of that stuff must've got lost in the move.
搬什么家? 我们没搬过啊
What move? We haven't moved.
发生了什么啊?
What's going on?
我很想告诉你 但是我保证要保密的
Oh! I want to tell you, but I promised to keep it a secret.
跟老婆不能有秘密
You can't have secrets from your wife!
我们结婚那么多年了 你现在才说
It's very late in the marriage to tell me that.
我把所有必需品都放在这堵假墙后面了
I've hidden all our supplies behind a fake wall.
我说地下室怎么变这么利索了
I thought the basement looked cleaner.
看到没? 我们逃生的包
See? These are our bug-out bags.
这里有我们生存的所有必需品
In here is everything we need to survive.
从何说起啊?
Survive what?
若隐若现的世界末日啊
The looming kablooey.
看到你那么担心未来我很欣慰
It's reassuring to see you're aware of the future,
但这个真的有点怪怪的
but this is all a little...creepy.
怪怪的?!
Creepy?!
Marge 世界末日即将到来
Marge, the apocalypse is coming.
也许是明天 也许永远不会来 但它在逼近我们
Maybe not tomorrow, maybe never,but it's coming.
而且很近
And soon.
我要睡觉去了
I'm going to bed.
这边没有把手啊
There's no handle on this side!
一个我无法准备的东西
The one thing I couldn't prepare for.
这里有我的小点心薯片
Oh, these here are my snack chips.
你的发泡奶酪 那些是涂鸦画
Your cheese puffs.Those are doodles.
除了橘子 我吃所有橘子颜色的东西
I will eat anything orange except an orange.
导师 是酷还是抽风呢?
这样就可以把小牛犊接生出来
And that's how you deliver a baby calf
使用马桶拔子
with a bathroom plunger.
E.M.P.?!
An E.M.P.?!
电磁冲击波
该咋办你懂的
You know what that means!
手动剪刀
Hand scissors.
再不给电弹劾你 赶紧供电 求解释
春田镇所有的电子设备都不能用了
All electronics in Springfield have been disabled.
连音乐卡片也不行
Even the musical greeting cards.
就是现在 逃生时间到了
This is it. Bug-out time.
我们之外的所有人都惨了
Everyone but us is doomed.
我感觉就像高富帅
I am so jazzed.
市长先生 你的管理层将采取何种措施确保社会稳定?
Mr. Mayor, what's your administration doing to ensure there's no panic?
我不知道 你的管理层又在干嘛?
I don't know. What is your administration doing?
我这就告诉你
There you have it.
一个没有法规 没有领导 没有电视的镇子
A town without rules, without leadership, without television.
这里是Kent Brockman 在和他自己说话
This is Kent Brockman, talking to himself.
Marge 就是现在 世界末日了
Marge, this is it, TEOTWAWKI!
语出REM乐队同名歌曲
我们预见的那个世界末日?
"The end of the world as we know it"?
孩子们在哪里?
Uh-huh. Where's the kids?
Lisa和Maggie在楼下 Bart和Millhouse在他房间里玩
Lisa and Maggie are downstairs, and Bart's in his room with Milhouse.
儿子 快上车
Boy, get in the car,
和你最好的朋友永别吧
and say good-bye to your best friend forever.
永别了 Millouse
Bye forever, Milhouse.
再会 Bart
See you, Bart.
这是我女儿
This is my daughter.
她可以给新世界带来音乐
She brings the gift of music to the new world.
- 那萨克斯是中音还是上低音的? - 上低音
- Is that sax alto or baritone? - Baritone.
这将会是个很漫长的世界末日
This is gonna be a long apocalypse.
难以置信
Ay, caramba!
确实难以置信
Ay, caramba indeed.
老爸 我们怎么可能在这儿度过余下的一生?
Dad, how are we supposed to spend the rest of our lives here?
现在已经开始无聊了
We're already bored.
我有个法子打发时间
Here's something to pass the endless time.
把传过同性恋绯闻的名人记下来
Write down which celebrities were rumored to be gay
给我们的子孙后代看
for future generations.
好的 老大
Yes, sir.
社会是不会再从零开始的
Society will not have to start from square one.
Homie 我从没想过会在厄运刚一降临时
Homie, I never thought we'd turn our backs on our love ones
就背叛我们所爱的人
at the first hint of trouble.
Marge 当我在为世界末日做准备时
Marge, when I started prepping for the end of the world,
所有人都取笑我
everyone laughed at me.
没有人取笑你
No one was laughing.
你一直在秘密进行
You kept it a secret!
不能因为这是我想象的 就否定其真实性
Well, just because I imagined it, doesn't make it any less true.
现在他们都只能靠自己了
And now all those people are on their own.
你怎么能自称为一个基督徒?
How can you call yourself a Christian?
如果耶稣有把枪 他能活到今天
If Jesus had a gun, he'd be alive today.
Homer Simpson
Homer Simpson!
我爱上你的时候
When I fell in love with you,
是因为你有一颗宽阔的胸怀和一张帅气的脸
it was because of your big heart and your good looks.
但总有一天 再帅的脸也会苍老的
But some day, those good looks are gonna fade.
不会吧?!
What?!
过不了多久我们就会被那些没有装备的人所包围
Soon we'll be approached by people who haven't prepared.
现在起不要直视他们的脸
Now, do not look at their faces.
这会让人产生怜悯与同情之心
That can trigger feelings and emotions,
而在《文明时代2.0: 怪人的崛起》中那是行不通的
which have no place in Civilization 2.0: Rise of the Weirdos.
我已经解决了此类问题
I may have solved that problem.
这是我改装的步枪瞄准仪
This rifle scope I modified
它会使任何一张人脸看起来都充满危险和攻击性
makes any human face look dangerous and threatening.
为什么要将他们全部击毙?
Why do we have to shoot them at all?
你能用刀达到同样效果?
Are you that good with a knife?
不 我想要帮助那些没做准备的人
No! I want to help the people who didn't prepare.
你为什么要向我开枪?
What'd you shoot me for?
你在想我是不是疯了 是不是?
You were thinking I'd gone mad with power, weren't you?!
没有 但我现在这么想了
I wasn't, but I am now.
天啊 什么情况?
Oh, God, now what?
每次你一大早把我们吵醒
Every time you wake us up early in the morning,
不是要去教堂 就是要我们改变身份
it's either church or we have to change our identities.
别乱想 Mary Ellen
Don't be silly, Mary Ellen.
我们现在得离开这个地方
Now we're going to leave this place.
对不起了 Bart
I'm sorry, Bart.
我知道你交了一个露营女朋友
I know you've made a bug-out camp girlfriend.
我得跟你说老实话
I've got to be honest with you.
那只是一袋米 我在上面画了张脸而已
It was just a bag of rice I drew a face on.
好米还是糙米?
White rice or brown?
我没注意过
I never noticed.
好孩子
Good boy.
我们要将这些补给品运回到春田镇
So we'll take these supplies back to Springfield
水
快 餐
净水药片
那儿的人急需要
where they're needed most.
你是个大好人 Homer Simpson
You're a good man, Homer Simpson.
自杀药片
A片
你说你把警报器的线切断了啊
You said you cut the wires to the alarm.
我确实是把什么东西的线给切断了
Hmm, I cut the wires to something.
50年冰淇淋供给
听好 大家伙儿 都把眼睛盯准了
Okay everybody, keep your eyes peeled
找一个不发亮的里程标 标着"23""36"还是多少的
for an unlit mile post marked "23" or "36" or something.
如果我们错过了就死定了
If we miss it, we're dead.
爸爸 后面有灯光跟着我们
Dad, there are lights following us.
怎么可能? 我把所有的汽油都拿走了啊
How can that be? I took every last can of gas.
好了 大家放松
Now, everyone relax
假装我们是要撞上一堵软砖墙
and pretend we're about to be hit by a soft brick wall.
别挡路 玉米
Out of our way, corn!
春田镇饥饿的人们
The starving people of Springfield
正迫切等待我们的罐装玉米 玉米片...
are desperately in need of our delivery of canned corn,
还有速冻玉米粒火速送到呢
corn flakes and flash frozen corn niblets!
我为你感到骄傲
I'm proud of you.
社会也许崩溃了 但是我们的道德永存
Society may have crumbled, but our decency hasn't.
现在就去拯救痛苦的灵魂
Now to save these sorry souls
让他们摆脱混乱饥饿以及为了繁衍而做爱的生活
from a life of anarchy, starvation and having sex for procreation.
一切都很正常
Oh, everything's normal.
世界没有毁灭
The world didn't end!
老爸 你说过人们会互饮对方的血的
Dad, you said people would be drinking each other's blood.
1984年战争电影
你把《赤色黎明》看上13遍也会这么说的
You got to watch a VHS copy of Red Dawn 13 times!
别再抱怨了
Stop complaining!
不是发生电磁冲击波了吗?
What happened with the E.M.P.?
春田镇只是停了会儿电
Only Springfield lost power,
几天之后就来电了
you see, and after a few days, it came back.
还比以前更亮堂了
Maybe a little bit brighter.
而且邻里间互帮互助的精神也涌现出来了
And the spirit of neighborly cooperation broke out
好像所有暴脾气的怪人都走了似的
as if all the weird, angry people had left.
社会没有崩溃?
Then society didn't crumble?
动物园里的动物没被吃掉?
The zoo animals weren't eaten?
没 好吧 是有那么几只
No-- well, a couple.
这次没有发生的灾难才是大灾难
This non-disaster is a catastrophe!
这世界没有毁灭 你就那么失望
Are you really so disappointed the world didn't end,
那么想证明你是对的?
just so you could be proven right?
不是的 不是的
No, no.
只是因为 在新世界里
It's just that, in the new world,
我也许能成为一个大人物
I would have been a big shot.
等不了多久的
Well, not for long.
我和其他人正在商量
Me and the others were planning
推翻你再把你禁闭在洞穴里
to overthrow you and seal you in a cave.
是嘛 但是你并不知道
Yeah, but what you didn't know
我会把你们所有的饮用水都下毒
was I was gonna poison all your drinking water.
所以我现在只喝自己的尿
Which is why I'm only drinking my own urine.
各位 难道大家没发觉就算是一个不完美的社会
Guys, can't you see that even an imperfect society
也比创造一个野蛮愚昧的新社会要好吗?
is better than the savagery of creating a new one?
我很高兴我们还拥有文明
I for one am glad we're stuck with civilization,
而且我认为我们还会拥有很长很长的时间
and I think we will be for a long, long time.
我饿了
I'm hungry.
听着 你可以现在就吃薯片
Look, you can have potato chips now,
或者再等个十分钟
or if you wait ten minutes,
就能随心所欲地吃脑子了
you can have all the brains you can eat.
我两样都要
I want both.
欢迎加入 SPS 辛普森一家字幕组 参与翻译后期
详情搜索 Google 或 新浪微博